export const questions = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "Question 1",
    answers: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "Question 1?",
    answers: ["Mars", "Venus", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: "Question 1'?",
    answers: ["Harper Lee", "J.K. Rowling", "Ernest Hemingway", "Jane Austen"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "Question 1?",
    answers: ["Seoul", "Beijing", "Tokyo", "Bangkok"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "Question 1?",
    answers: ["Oxygen", "Gold", "Silver", "Iron"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "Question 1?",
    answers: ["1912", "1920", "1905", "1931"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "Question 1?",
    answers: ["Elephant", "Blue Whale", "Giraffe", "Hippopotamus"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "Question 1?",
    answers: ["Leonardo da Vinci", "Vincent van Gogh", "Pablo Picasso", "Claude Monet"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question: "Question 1?",
    answers: ["Euro", "Dollar", "Pound", "Australian Dollar"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: "Question 1?",
    answers: ["Tomato", "Avocado", "Onion", "Cilantro"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
];
